[
    {
        "question": "💡🟥🍾🟩",
        "answer": "灯红酒绿"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧔⛏➔⛰️",
        "answer": "愚公移山"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍃👱‍♂️❤️🐲☠️",
        "answer": "叶公好龙"
    },
    {
        "question": "⭕🛶🔍🗡",
        "answer": "刻舟求剑"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌿🛶🤲🏻🏹",
        "answer": "草船借箭"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑‍🦯💆🐘",
        "answer": "盲人摸象"
    },
    {
        "question": "👉🏽🦌➔🐴",
        "answer": "指鹿为马"
    },
    {
        "question": "👄🥶🦷💀",
        "answer": "唇寒齿亡"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦩🦪⚔️",
        "answer": "鹬蚌相争"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦊❌🐯🆗",
        "answer": "狐假虎威"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐦💀🏹🚫",
        "answer": "鸟尽弓藏"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌊➡️🦁️🤬",
        "answer": "河东狮吼"
    },
    {
        "question": "🪵🌝🌛🐇",
        "answer": "守株待兔"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍺🐂🐅🐅",
        "answer": "九牛二虎"
    },
    {
        "question": "💬🙅🏼‍♀️",
        "answer": "欲言又止"
    },
    {
        "question": "🖕🌊⛰️",
        "answer": "指点江山"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧍‍♀️👩‍👩‍👧‍👦🧑‍🤝‍🧑👨‍👨‍👦‍👦",
        "answer": "人五人六"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍑🍑👨‍👦‍👦",
        "answer": "二桃三士"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦜📖👅",
        "answer": "鹦鹉学舌"
    },
    {
        "question": "❤️🔀",
        "answer": "一心二意"
    }
]